<?xml version="1.0" ?><mod name="erlking" version="0"><scene name="givenToTheHounds"><t>&lt;i&gt;“How disappointing,”&lt;/i&gt; drips the refined voice of the Erlking.  His horse’s hooves thud softly on the ground as he walks below you.  The cane at his side clicks against the forest floor with every other step.  You have just enough wherewithal to understand his words as your fingers grip the net.

&lt;i&gt;“This was but a few minutes’ diversion.  I had been hoping for more of a challenge,”&lt;/i&gt; he says, the red glow in his eyes dimming.  &lt;i&gt;“You’re not particularly good at this, are you?”&lt;/i&gt; he says, sighing.  His long face looks almost wistful.

&lt;i&gt;“Perhaps next time,”&lt;/i&gt; he sighs.  He turns, his dark cloak flaring.  Is it your imagination or do his golden antlers seem a bit more dull?

You allow yourself a brief moment of relief as he turns his attention from you.

&lt;i&gt;“But it would be wrong to not reward my Hounds for a job well done.”&lt;/i&gt;  His cane flashes with golden light as he slashes it against the support rope.

The fog swallows the Erlking as you drop to the ground.  The impact against the mossy forest floor doesn’t injure you, but it &lt;b&gt;does&lt;/b&gt; knock the wind from you.  As you struggle to regain your breath, you inhale the icy fog, and a cascade of terror... and something else... runs through you.

This fear doubles as the two hounds waste no time.  They are on you in the space of a heartbeat, ripping the net from around you with teeth, their powerful paws shoving you to all fours as they snarl and bark.  Their red, shiny dog cocks slip from their heavy sheaths, throbbing with thin, purple veins.  The fog has definitely done something to you, because you can’t help but lick your lips at the sight.

Growling, the first Hound presses his paws to your [ass], sinking his claws roughly into your flesh.  He rips your [armor] from you with a low snarl.  You feel a rush of warmth as his muzzle presses between your [ass],</t><if test="CreatureTestSex(player,[2, 3])"><t> long tongue touching the bottom edge of your [vagina]</t><elseif test="CreatureHasTrait(player,'testicles',false)"></elseif><t> long tongue lapping at the base of your balls</t><elseif test="CreatureTestSex(player,[1, 3])"></elseif><t> long tongue lapping at the base of your cock and along your [vagina]</t><else></else><t> long tongue slapping warmly against your taint</t></if><t> before running up to your [asshole].

You shiver, the fog-born fear still controlling your body.  You feel a rush of strange gratitude— the hounds don’t want to eat you, they just want to sate a different hunger.  And with the mindbending fog inside you, you want desperately to satisfy them.  Your submissive mind even hopes that if you can do a good job, they’ll spare you any further domination.  You’d be repulsed by the idea of fucking two Hounds to exhaustion if you weren’t so damn scared of them.  An errant thought at the back of your mind hopes that the effects of this fog are only temporary.

You glance over your shoulder, wanting to make sure the Hound has no trouble getting into you,</t><if test="CreatureHasTrait(player,'taur',true)"><t> and realizing that you’re too tall, you fold your legs beneath you, dropping all the way to the ground,</t></if><t> when the other hound suddenly mounts you from the front, paw shoving your</t><if test="player.femininity&lt;30"><t> strong jaw</t><elseif test="player.femininity&gt;70"></elseif><t> delicate chin</t><else></else><t> chin</t></if><t>towards his massive, slimy dog cock.  You get a brief glimpse of a crystal-clear bead of pre before the tip is forced between your lips.

The Hound begins fucking your face roughly, leaving salty precum on your tongue, his cock throbbing between your lips.  You feel grateful that the Hound has chosen to simply fuck you, and you want nothing more than to do the best job possible for the Hound.You groan around the Hound’s dick as you feel a pressure against your [asshole].  The beast kneads his paws into your [ass] cheeks before he grips you between the haunches. A brief moment passes before he shoves his foot-long doggie cock into your rear. </t><command>StretchAnus(player,36,false)</command><t> You yelp, realizing what’s to come, and try to wriggle away, but, mounted by the two Hounds, there’s no escape.  The Hounds growl in unison and you freeze, cowed by the two powerful males who want their way with your frightened, vulnerable body.

After all, comes a thought in your fog-addled head, they’ve earned the right to do whatever they want to their prey.

It doesn’t take the two feral canines long.  They rock back and forth, shoving their thick cocks in and out of your submissive, helpless body.  The one in front slides his paws from your shoulders to the back of your head, burying your [face] into his crotch, so deep that your tongue licks against the throbbing bulge of his knot, your nose buried in the thick fur above his shaft.</t><if test="CreatureHasTrait(player,'tails',false)"><t>  The Hound behind bites onto your [onetail], tugging it dominantly as he thrusts over and over into your [asshole].</t><else></else><t>  The Hound behind grips between your haunches all the harder, thrusting into your [ass] again and again.</t></if><t>  You tremble, completely dominated by the two powerful ferals as they make you their prey-bitch.

They cum within moments of each other, the one in front driving his huge knot into your mouth, leaving your jaw aching.  You groan in protest as his cock shoots hot seed down your throat.  Nearly gagging on the canine dick already, there’s little you can do but swallow the Hound’s cum.  As you gurgle it down, you feel the Hound behind you painfully shove his thick knot into your ass.  You try to scream, but with a mouth full of cock and cum, there’s little you can do but take it like prey.  Your body quakes, belly swelling as you’re filled with cum at both ends leaving you warm, bloated, and strangely satisfied.

You shiver, breathing in the cold, mind-altering fog, waiting obediently for the two Hounds to tire of you.  Oddly enough, with their seeds spent, they’re strangely affectionate, and you find your back, face, and ass covered in warm, languid licks from the two canines.  Eventually their knots shrink, and the two Hounds withdraw from you, letting you slump to the ground as they pad off into the woods.  

As the fog recedes, your mind quickly returns.  Blinking, you wobble to your [feet], wiping cum from your lips and gathering your scattered gear from around the clearing before setting back for camp.  You find a shiny, red pepper in the clearing, but appear to have dropped some gems in your failed flight from the Hunt.

</t></scene></mod>