<?xml version="1.0" ?><mod name="hellhound" version="0"><scene name="encounter"><t>You hear a fiery howl as a demonic, two-headed beast-man leaps out in front of you!</t><comment>TODO: move from code codex entry unlock</comment><command>ShowSprite('s_hellhound')</command><battle monster="hellhound"></battle></scene><scene name="hellhoundRapesPlayer"><if test="player.HP &gt; 0"><t>Overcome by sexual desire, you submit to the hungry hellhound.

</t><else></else><t>Too weak to continue fighting, you fall to your knees.

</t></if><t>The heads of the hellhound grin with desire as he rises onto his hind legs. As the hellhound stands before you, your eyes widen at the sight of its equipment: a pair of eight-inch long black rods, one above the other, with a sack containing a quad of flaming balls underneath. As the hound swaggers closer, you gulp at the thought of what those fiery balls are going to be pumping into you. You are helpless against the hellhound as he pushes you onto your </t><if test="CreatureTestLegType(player,true,'HOOFED')"><t>hocks and knees</t><else></else><t>hands and knees</t></if><t> and positions himself behind you. He grips you with his clawed hands on your shoulders and easily holds you in place. The powerful creature is easily able to get past your [armor] and you feel one of his rods brush against your [butt].  A shudder shoots through your body as he brings his two heads down to either side of your own, his hot canine breath blowing past your ears. He stays there for a few moments, completely still... before suddenly pulling his heads back and </t><if test="CreatureTestSex(player,[2, 3]) and CreatureHasTrait(player,'naga',true)"><t>slamming his twin dicks into your [vagina] and your [ass].  </t><if test="player.vaginalCapacity() &lt; monster.cockArea()"><t>You feel an intense mixture of sensations in your lower body as your [asshole] feels like it is being torn apart, while your [vagina] is filled with an intense pleasure at being filled with the creature's large member.  </t><else></else><t>Your lower body explodes with pain as the hellhound forces himself in too quickly for either your [asshole] or your [vagina] to handle.  </t></if><else></else><t>slamming his lower dick into your [asshole], while rubbing the other between the cheeks of your [butt].  </t></if></scene></mod>