<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><mod name="mindbreaker" version="1"><state><var name="timesVisited">0</var></state><scene name="encounter"><text name="first"><t>Curiosity triumphs against your better judgment and you decide to continue exploring. You keep moving through the lightless reaches, your footsteps echoing on the damp ground when something slimy grapples you from behind. You struggle, but your weapon has been thrown on the floor and whatever grabbed you is crawling around in your hair. With your arms tightly bound in place, you hear a giggle as the disgusting thing finds your ear, enters, and…&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You suddenly don’t care anymore. Why were you struggling? These things aren’t disgusting at all, and they are very pleasurable. Squelch, squelch, squelch is all you hear for a few seconds and you shake your head as lights flash behind your eyelids. You think you are still shaking but you lack feedback from your body. A green song knits loud spaghetti and asks you in reverse when snowball is.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;[say:Woefully inadequate], you hear yourself say, not feeling your mouth move at all. This is all so weird, and yet so hot somehow. Kaerb-Dnim laughs and you laugh too. How could you ever forget about her? Kaerb-Dnim was your friend and lover. You always used to play naughty games together when you were younger. Now, this is just another one of those games. Squelch, squelch, squelch again and you feel a hand, her hand, slowly caress one of your breasts, making you moan appreciatively…&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;More squelches later, you're helping her pale-skinned hand down into your pussy in order to continue playing as you mindlessly drool in pleasure. You have to roleplay as a complete slut while she pretends to be your mistress, right? Yes, that was it, and aren’t you good at playing the slut? Her tentacles groping your boobs feels so good and the slime they leave makes your skin all glossy and wet, too. This is just how you like it.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A few hours later, as you orgasm for the tenth time, your friend finally lets you rest.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;[say:We will see each other again… come to me when you are lonely and we can resume the game.]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You leave, still giddy from the action. It only occurs to you once you are out of the cave that you never had a friend named Kaerb-Dnim, let alone saw a thing like her before in Ingnam. Yet, despite this contradiction, you have the impulse to come and see her again. </t><set op="add" value="1" var="timesVisited"/></text><text name="second"><t>You hurry and go meet your friend Kaerb-Dnim inside, nearly jumping in her arms when you find her waiting for you.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As soon as you embrace her, you can feel her lovely tentacles caress your hair, going for your ears. You shake your head as lights flash behind your eyelids. You think you are still shaking but you lack feedback from your body. A green song knits loud spaghetti and asks you in reverse when snowball is.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;[say:Woefully inadequate], you hear yourself say, not feeling your mouth at all. This is so weird yet so hot. Kaerb-Dnim laughs and you laugh as well, both of you resume the game where you left it. Having her tentacle in your head is the best! You could let her fuck your ears all day long and still want to do it the day after.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Squelch, squelch, squelch is all you hear for a few seconds as her hand slowly caresses your left breast making you moan appreciatively. You touch her hand and proceed to kiss her passionately as she methodically delivers pleasure to your mind, wet noises echoing all around the cave.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;More squelches later and you're helping her pale-skinned hand down into your pussy in order to continue playing, as you mindlessly drool in pleasure. You have to roleplay as a complete slut while she pretends to be your mistress, and aren’t you good at playing the slut? Her tentacles groping your boobs feel so good, and the slime they leave make your skin all glossy and wet, too. This is just how you like it.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A few hours later as you orgasm for the hundredth time, your friend finally lets you rest. The ground is still covered with all the juice your pussy drooled. It was even more messy than the last time&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;[say:Come to me again when you are ready and we can continue making you even better.]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You leave, still giddy of the action. It only occurs to you once you are out of the cave that you never had a friend named Kaerb-Dnim, let alone saw a thing like her before in Ingnam. Yet, despite this contradiction, you have the impulse to come and see her again. You feel your mind become more lustful, colorful, and perfect. Just like after each visit.</t><set op="add" value="1" var="timesVisited"/></text><text name="final"><t>You, yet again, enter the cave and cheerfully rush to meet Kaerb-Dnim, who welcomes you with open arms.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;[say:I see you have become as slutty and lusty for me as I wanted, [name]. I think it’s high time I reward your efforts, and give you your well-deserved prize.]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You cheerfully nod, letting her put her loving tentacle back into your head, drooling at the mere thought of your mind becoming more lewd and obscene. This drives you to the edge, making you cum spontaneously as you feel your mind being probed again. Squelch squelch squelch is all you hear for a few seconds, and you shake your head as lights flash behind your eyelids. You think you are still shaking but you lack feedback from your body. A green song knits loud spaghetti and asks you in reverse when snowball is.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;[say:Woefully inadequate], you hear yourself say, not feeling your mouth at all. Kaerb-Dnim laughs. You laugh yet again as she kisses you, her tentacle coiling around your breasts, tweaking your nipples as you fiercely masturbate under her guidance. Soon Kaerb-Dnim guides you down to the ground and proceeds to grind her lovely purple pussy against your snatch, locking your legs against hers. The pair of you grind for several minutes, your pussies sliding against each other until Kaerb-Dnim finally cums.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Something, not unlike a mass of tentacles, slides between her pussy and yours, and you gleefully let it in, orgasming as it squirms inside you for a minute and heads past your cervix to settle in your womb, depositing something. She finally breaks away from you, her lovely tentacles retreating back out of your oozing snatch.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;[say:We can finally be true sisters, [name], isn’t that wonderful?]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You only understand everything a few seconds later as you start shaking uncontrollably in pleasure. Being a true sister to Kaerb-Dnim? What a wonderful thing! You’re so happy this is happening to you as you feel something hatch within you.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your womb aches and tingles pleasurably just as you start changing. It feels so good to be entirely remade from the inside and you cum several times as your skin slowly turns to a pale ghostly shade, not unlike that of Kaerb-Dnim, and begins spreading from your belly. You moan in delight as your hair falls from your head, and are replaced by purple tentacles of various size, which you use to fuck your own brain right away. You open your many new eyes located on your tentacles smiling blissfully as the thing below your waist shifts into eight tentacles webbed to each other like a night dress. Your chest is left somewhat intact, although your are covered with a webbed exoskeleton, similar to your legs. From afar, one would think you're wearing a gothic leather dress, until they'd notice it's a part of your body. You moan in delight, groping your own breast at the pleasure of your new, lewd and corrupted body. Kaerb-Dnim closes in on you as you molest yourself&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;[say:You enjoy it, don’t you? Don’t you pity those that can’t enjoy such sensations?]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You giggle lustfully understanding her request right away. [say:Yes sister, I think everyone in Mareth and beyond should live like this.]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A wicked plan starts to form in your mind. You imagine everyone living in an endless orgy of constant mind shattering pleasure, as you create an entire sorority of creatures like you. The entire world is now playing the game, a game you and sister Kaerb-Dnim truly share now. Obviously you and Kaerb-Dnim, now the sorority founders, need new willing sisters and minions. It’s high time you get out and find more willing, or unwilling, people to join in on your perverted games. Then, once you have achieved greater numbers, you can paint Mareth green and white with fluids.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;You now are a Mindbreaker &lt;/b&gt;</t></text><if test="timesVisited eq 0"><t>As you wander the mountain you enter a tunnel where light does not penetrate far. For a moment you think that you may have lost your way, but decide to explore the tunnel regardless. The deeper you go, the less you can see, and there is a weird feeling inside of you that tells you perhaps you should be elsewhere . Do you continue? Warning &lt;b&gt;-Content in this cave is not for everyone. It includes mind break, tentacles, parasitism and severe slutification. Proceed at your own risk.- &lt;/b&gt;</t><display ref="first"/><elseif test="player.cor lt 90 or timesVisited lt 2"/><t>You approach the cave again, and the image of your friend Kaerb-Dnim waiting for you inside assaults your mind. Do you enter? </t><display ref="second"/><else/><t>You approach the cave where your friend, Kaerb-Dnim, awaits you. You're finally as lusty and slutty as you should be! Winning the game should be a piece of cake, yet a faint voice in your head tells you something terrible is about to happen if you enter that cave. You're going to enter, right? </t><display ref="final"/></if></scene></mod>